{
	"response_code": "0",
	"results": [
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Music",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "Rapper Snoop Dogg&#039;s real name is &#039;Cordozar Calvin Broadus, Jr.&#039;.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Music",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "The cover of The Beatles album &quot;Abbey Road&quot; featured a Volkswagen Beetle in the background.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Music",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "Norwegian producer Kygo released a remix of the song &quot;Sexual Healing&quot; by Marvin Gaye.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Music",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "The country song  &ldquo;A Boy Named Sue&rdquo; was written by Shel Silverstein.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Music",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "Ashley Frangipane performs under the stage name Halsey.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Music",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "&quot;The Division Bell&quot; is the final album of the progressive rock band Pink Floyd.",
			"correct_answer": "False",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"True"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Music",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "&quot;Twenty One Pilots&quot; made the song &quot;The Motion&quot; featuring Sampha.",
			"correct_answer": "False",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"True"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Music",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "EDM label Monstercat signs tracks instead of artists.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Music",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "For his performance at ComplexCon 2016 in Long Beach, California, Skrillex revived his &quot;Mothership&quot; set piece for one night only.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
				
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Music",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "medium",
			"question": "3 members of 2 Live Crew were arrested for playing songs from their album, As Nasty As They Wanna Be, live.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
				
			]
		}
	]
}